https://hardyferns.org//privacy-policy/

Fern Info
Fern DatabaseCultural InfoPropagationGenus CharacteristicsGlossary
Resources
Affiliated GardensGrowers and VendorsFern WebsitesFern BooksHFF Quarterlies
NewsContact
Hardy Fern Foundation
Public display, information and education about ferns
0
Join Now!
Cookies
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the U.S. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. The Hardy Fern Foundation uses reports by Google Analytics so we can better understand website traffic and usage.
Who we share your data with
We do not share your data with anyone.
How long we retain your data
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
The Hardy Fern Foundation
Mail: PO Box 3797, Federal Way, WA 98063-3797
Telephone: (253) 838-4646
Fax: (253) 838-4686
Email:  hff@rhodygarden.org
©2020 The Hardy Fern Foundation
PO Box 3797
Federal Way, WA 98063-3797
